{
  {
    "prompt":"What does a baby computer call his father?",
    "response":"Data"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"After an unsuccessful harvest, why did the farmer decide to try a career in music?",
    "response":"Because he had a ton of sick beets."
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Why is it so cheap to throw a party at a haunted house?",
    "response":"Because the ghosts bring all the boo's."
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Which days are the strongest?",
    "response":"Saturday and Sunday, the rest are weekdays"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Why shouldn't you fart in an Apple store?",
    "response":"Because they don't have Windows"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What is the most popular fish in the ocean?",
    "response":"A starfish"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"How do cows stay up to date on the world?",
    "response":"They read the Moo-spaper "
  },  
  {
    "prompt":"Where do pirates get their hooks?",
    "response":"Second hand stores"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What do you call a line of men waiting to get haircuts?",
    "response":"A barberqueue."
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What do you call a beehive without an exit?",
    "response":"Un-bee-leave-able"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What happens when it rains cats and dogs?",
    "response":"You have to be careful not to step in a poodle"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What kind of bagel can fly?",
    "response":"A plain bagel."
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What did one snowman say to the other snow man?",
    "response":"Do you smell carrot?"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Why do Astronauts use Macs?",
    "response":"You can't open Windows in space!"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What do you call a chicken that loves counting her eggs?",
    "response":"A mathemachicken."
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Why doesn't the sun go to school?",
    "response":"It's already got a million degrees!"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What do you call a beehive with no exit?",
    "response":"Unbelievable"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"How do you weigh Millennials?",
    "response":"In Instagrams"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What did the pirate say on his 80th birthday?",
    "response":"Aye Matey (I'm eighty)"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"Why did the near-sighted man fall into the hole?",
    "response":"Because he couldn't see that well"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"What's the difference between the bird flu and the swine flu?"
    "response":"One requires tweetment and the other oinkment"
  },
  {
    "prompt":"",
    "response":""
  },
}
